[{"questionText":"Vad heter Han Solos rymdskepp?","alternatives":["A) X-wing","B) TIE Fighter","C) Millennium Falcon","D) Slave I"],"correctAnswer":2,"visible":true},{"questionText":"Vem är Luke Skywalkers syster?","alternatives":["A) Rey","B) Padmé Amidala","C) Ahsoka Tano","D) Leia Organa"],"correctAnswer":3,"visible":false},{"questionText":"Vad heter planeten där Anakin Skywalker växer upp?","alternatives":["A) Tatooine","B) Coruscant","C) Naboo","D) Endor"],"correctAnswer":0,"visible":false},{"questionText":"Vad heter den röda sith-lorden med horn på huvudet?","alternatives":["A) Count Dooku","B) Kylo Ren","C) Darth Maul","D) General Grievous"],"correctAnswer":2,"visible":false},{"questionText":"Vad betyder \"Sith\" i Star Wars?","alternatives":["A) En uråldrig orden av mörka Jedi","B) En speciell typ av ljussabel","C) En titel för imperieofficerare","D) En ras av utomjordingar"],"correctAnswer":0,"visible":false},{"questionText":"Vem dödar kejsare Palpatine i Return of the Jedi?","alternatives":["A) Luke Skywalker","B) Darth Vader","C) Yoda","D) Obi-Wan Kenobi"],"correctAnswer":1,"visible":false},{"questionText":"Vad är namnet på Obi-Wan Kenobis klonkommendör under Klonkrigen?","alternatives":["A) Captain Rex","B) Commander Cody","C) Commander Fox","D) Commander Coby"],"correctAnswer":1,"visible":false},{"questionText":"Vad är namnet på Ahsoka Tano's klonkommendör under Klonkrigen?","alternatives":["A) Captain Rex","B) Commander Cody","C) Commander Fox","D) Commander Coby"],"correctAnswer":0,"visible":false},{"questionText":"Vad heter metalllegeringen som gör Mandalorians rustningar så starka?","alternatives":["A) Durasteel","B) Cortosis","C) Beskar","D) Neuranium"],"correctAnswer":2,"visible":false},{"questionText":"Vilken karaktär säger först \"I have a bad feeling about this\" i A New Hope?","alternatives":["A) Han Solo","B) Luke Skywalker","C) Obi-Wan Kenobi","D) C-3PO"],"correctAnswer":1,"visible":false},{"questionText":"What is the name of the Sith homeworld in Star Wars lore?","alternatives":["A) Exegol","B) Moraband","C) Dathomir","D) Malachor"],"correctAnswer":1,"visible":false},{"questionText":"What is the real name of the species that Yoda belongs to?","alternatives":["A) Lannik","B) Yodalan","C) Zeffonian","D) Unknown"],"correctAnswer":3,"visible":false},{"questionText":"What is the name of General Grievous' flagship, which Anakin and Obi-Wan board in Revenge of the Sith?","alternatives":["A) The Invisible Hand","B) The Malevolence","C) The Executrix","D) The Devastator"],"correctAnswer":0,"visible":false},{"questionText":"What is the full designation of the stormtrooper who defects and becomes Finn?","alternatives":["A) TK-421","B) FN-2187","C) CT-7567","D) RC-1138"],"correctAnswer":1,"visible":false},{"questionText":"Which ancient Sith Lord was known for discovering the secret to eternal life?","alternatives":["A) Darth Nihilus","B) Darth Bane","C) Darth Plagueis","D) Darth Revan"],"correctAnswer":2,"visible":false},{"questionText":"What species is Admiral Ackbar?","alternatives":["A) Mon Calamari","B) Quarren","C) Nautolan","D) Rodian"],"correctAnswer":0,"visible":false},{"questionText":"What is the maximum number of blades a standard lightsaber can have in traditional Jedi combat?","alternatives":["A) 1","B) 2","C) 3","D) 4"],"correctAnswer":1,"visible":false},{"questionText":"Who was the first Jedi to wield a purple lightsaber in Star Wars canon?","alternatives":["A) Mace Windu","B) Revan","C) Plo Koon","D) Anakin Skywalker"],"correctAnswer":0,"visible":false},{"questionText":"What is the name of the Mandalorian artifact that determines the ruler of Mandalore?","alternatives":["A) The Mythosaur Skull","B) The Darksaber","C) The Mandalorian Crown","D) The Beskar Relic"],"correctAnswer":1,"visible":false},{"questionText":"Who is the first Jedi to fight Darth Sidious in Revenge of the Sith?","alternatives":["A) Obi-Wan Kenobi","B) Yoda","C) Mace Windu","D) Kit Fisto"],"correctAnswer":2,"visible":false},{"questionText":"What is the name of the podracing event Anakin Skywalker wins in The Phantom Menace?","alternatives":["A) The Boonta Eve Classic","B) The Tatooine Grand Prix","C) The Outer Rim Rally","D) The Hutt Cup"],"correctAnswer":0,"visible":false},{"questionText":"Which planet serves as the headquarters for the Jedi Order in the prequels?","alternatives":["A) Naboo","B) Coruscant","C) Kamino","D) Alderaan"],"correctAnswer":1,"visible":false},{"questionText":"Who orders the creation of the Clone Army?","alternatives":["A) Darth Sidious","B) Count Dooku","C) Master Sifo-Dyas","D) Chancellor Valorum"],"correctAnswer":2,"visible":false},{"questionText":"What is the name of Anakin Skywalker's Padawan in The Clone Wars series?","alternatives":["A) Aayla Secura","B) Asajj Ventress","C) Ahsoka Tano","D) Barriss Offee"],"correctAnswer":2,"visible":false},{"questionText":"What color is Captain Rex's armor?","alternatives":["A) Red and white","B) Blue and white","C) Green and yellow","D) Black and gray"],"correctAnswer":1,"visible":false},{"questionText":"Who is the leader of the Separatist droid army?","alternatives":["A) General Grievous","B) Count Dooku","C) Darth Sidious","D) Nute Gunray"],"correctAnswer":0,"visible":false},{"questionText":"Which clone battalion fights under the command of Obi-Wan Kenobi?","alternatives":["A) 501st Legion","B) 104th Wolfpack Battalion","C) 212th Attack Battalion","D) 41st Elite Corps"],"correctAnswer":2,"visible":false},{"questionText":"Who is the Sith assassin that often works for Count Dooku?","alternatives":["A) Darth Maul","B) Asajj Ventress","C) Savage Opress","D) Cad Bane"],"correctAnswer":1,"visible":false},{"questionText":"Which Jedi Master fights Jango Fett on Kamino in Attack of the Clones?","alternatives":["A) Ki-Adi-Mundi","B) Plo Koon","C) Obi-Wan Kenobi","D) Mace Windu"],"correctAnswer":2,"visible":false},{"questionText":"What lightsaber fighting style does Count Dooku specialize in?","alternatives":["A) Form I: Shii-Cho","B) Form III: Soresu","C) Form II: Makashi","D) Form VII: Juyo"],"correctAnswer":2,"visible":false},{"questionText":"What famous line does Anakin Skywalker say before attacking the Jedi Temple in Revenge of the Sith?","alternatives":["A) \"I am the chosen one!\"","B) \"Execute Order 66.\"","C) \"The Jedi are traitors to the Republic.\"","D) \"You underestimate my power!\""],"correctAnswer":2,"visible":false},{"questionText":"Where is General Grievous' hideout in Revenge of the Sith?","alternatives":["A) Geonosis","B) Kashyyyk","C) Mustafar","D) Utapau"],"correctAnswer":3,"visible":false},{"questionText":"Which planet is completely covered in oceans and is home to the cloning facilities?","alternatives":["A) Kamino","B) Felucia","C) Naboo","D) Mon Cala"],"correctAnswer":0,"visible":false},{"questionText":"Where is Anakin Skywalker when he first meets Padmé Amidala?","alternatives":["A) Naboo","B) Coruscant","C) Tatooine","D) Mustafar"],"correctAnswer":2,"visible":false}]